{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Door Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40028/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40028,"taskName":"Doors - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Interior or Exterior Doors","xmTaskDescriptor":"Door Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":56,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Doors wood french entry latch","textMessagingName":"Repr Door","rolloverLongDesc":"Done by specialty firms \u0026 a few handymen with good sources for parts. Includes door parts \u0026 opening, closing \u0026 latching mechanisms \u0026 screens. Note separate categories for glass replacement, sliding glass doors, locksmith, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes hardware, locks, \u0026 latches.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Interior or Exterior Doors.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Door Repairs | Repair Interior or Exterior Doors \u003cin_city\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":22,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Door Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Doors - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Door Project","urlName":"Doors-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Door Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Front Door Repairs","searchKeywords":"Doors,wood,french,entry,latch,front,entry,sticking,threshold,double","emcCategoryOid":-12024,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":352,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40028/":{"taskOID":40028,"originalTaskOID":40028,"setID":352,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1414,"questionDisplayText":"Door Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of door needs to be repaired?  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2646,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"French","answerDisplayText":"French","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5783,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sliding","answerDisplayText":"Sliding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6126,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Storm and/or screen","answerDisplayText":"Storm and/or screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7066,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Wood composite","answerDisplayText":"Wood composite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2806,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1416,"questionDisplayText":"Damaged Parts/Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select all parts of the door or frame that are damaged.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3644,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lockset","answerDisplayText":"Lockset","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Knob","answerDisplayText":"Knob","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1833,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Deadbolt","answerDisplayText":"Deadbolt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3016,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hinge","answerDisplayText":"Hinge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5503,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Screen","answerDisplayText":"Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6342,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Threshold","answerDisplayText":"Threshold","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2617,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Frame","answerDisplayText":"Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6169,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stuck open or closed","answerDisplayText":"Stuck open or closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1918,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Difficult to open","answerDisplayText":"Difficult to open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2022,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Door sticks","answerDisplayText":"Door sticks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2031,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Door won't stay closed","answerDisplayText":"Door won't stay closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2011,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Door is cracking","answerDisplayText":"Door is cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2013,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Door is splitting","answerDisplayText":"Door is splitting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2027,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Door won't clear new flooring","answerDisplayText":"Door won't clear new flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6927,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Weather stripping","answerDisplayText":"Weather stripping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6447,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Track for sliding door","answerDisplayText":"Track for sliding door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1692,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Cracked glass","answerDisplayText":"Cracked glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3897,"answerDisplaySequence":18,"answerText":"Moisture between panes of insulated glass","answerDisplayText":"Moisture between panes of insulated glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":19,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1414,"questionDisplayText":"Door Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of door needs to be repaired?  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2646,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"French","answerDisplayText":"French","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5783,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sliding","answerDisplayText":"Sliding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6126,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Storm and/or screen","answerDisplayText":"Storm and/or screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7066,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Wood composite","answerDisplayText":"Wood composite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2806,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2646,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"French","answerDisplayText":"French","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5783,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sliding","answerDisplayText":"Sliding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6126,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Storm and/or screen","answerDisplayText":"Storm and/or screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7066,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Wood composite","answerDisplayText":"Wood composite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2806,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1416,"questionDisplayText":"Damaged Parts/Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select all parts of the door or frame that are damaged.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3644,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lockset","answerDisplayText":"Lockset","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Knob","answerDisplayText":"Knob","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1833,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Deadbolt","answerDisplayText":"Deadbolt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3016,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hinge","answerDisplayText":"Hinge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5503,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Screen","answerDisplayText":"Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6342,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Threshold","answerDisplayText":"Threshold","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2617,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Frame","answerDisplayText":"Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6169,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stuck open or closed","answerDisplayText":"Stuck open or closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1918,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Difficult to open","answerDisplayText":"Difficult to open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2022,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Door sticks","answerDisplayText":"Door sticks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2031,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Door won't stay closed","answerDisplayText":"Door won't stay closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2011,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Door is cracking","answerDisplayText":"Door is cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2013,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Door is splitting","answerDisplayText":"Door is splitting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2027,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Door won't clear new flooring","answerDisplayText":"Door won't clear new flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6927,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Weather stripping","answerDisplayText":"Weather stripping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6447,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Track for sliding door","answerDisplayText":"Track for sliding door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1692,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Cracked glass","answerDisplayText":"Cracked glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3897,"answerDisplaySequence":18,"answerText":"Moisture between panes of insulated glass","answerDisplayText":"Moisture between panes of insulated glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":19,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3644,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lockset","answerDisplayText":"Lockset","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Knob","answerDisplayText":"Knob","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1833,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Deadbolt","answerDisplayText":"Deadbolt","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3016,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hinge","answerDisplayText":"Hinge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5503,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Screen","answerDisplayText":"Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6342,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Threshold","answerDisplayText":"Threshold","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2617,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Frame","answerDisplayText":"Frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6169,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stuck open or closed","answerDisplayText":"Stuck open or closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1918,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Difficult to open","answerDisplayText":"Difficult to open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2022,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Door sticks","answerDisplayText":"Door sticks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2031,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Door won't stay closed","answerDisplayText":"Door won't stay closed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2011,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Door is cracking","answerDisplayText":"Door is cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2013,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Door is splitting","answerDisplayText":"Door is splitting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2027,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Door won't clear new flooring","answerDisplayText":"Door won't clear new flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6927,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Weather stripping","answerDisplayText":"Weather stripping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6447,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Track for sliding door","answerDisplayText":"Track for sliding door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1692,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Cracked glass","answerDisplayText":"Cracked glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3897,"answerDisplaySequence":18,"answerText":"Moisture between panes of insulated glass","answerDisplayText":"Moisture between panes of insulated glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":19,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}